{
    "subject": "resource/Summitville,_New_York",
    "predicate": "ontology/timeZone",
    "object": "resource/Eastern_Time_Zone",
    "human_readable": "Summitville, New York is in Eastern Time Zone.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9702885150909424,
            "question": "What time zone is Summitville, New York in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9525706768035889,
            "question": "Is Summitville, New York located in the Central Time Zone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8127366900444031,
            "question": "Name a city located in the same time zone as Summitville."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7309762239456177,
            "question": "When would it be noon in Summitville, New York?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45903101563453674,
            "question": "How does daylight saving time affect Summitville?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3679622411727905,
            "question": "If it is 10:00 AM in Summitville, what time is it in Los Angeles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2730192542076111,
            "question": "What region of the United States observes Eastern Time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1728215515613556,
            "question": "What is the purpose of time zones?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1569732278585434,
            "question": "How many time zones are there in the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12032855302095413,
            "question": "What are the benefits of having different time zones?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Summitville, New York is in Eastern Time Zone.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9231_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How many time zones are there in the United States?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9231_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the purpose of time zones?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9231_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What region of the United States observes Eastern Time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9231_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9231_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9231_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9231_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9231_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9231_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9231_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9231_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9231_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9231_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9231_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Summitville, New York is located in the Eastern Time Zone and provides details on when it follows Eastern Standard Time (EST) and Eastern Daylight Time (EDT). Therefore, the statement \"Summitville, New York is in Eastern Time Zone\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}